tryleanspa.com 2011-05-31

# Get leanspa

Privacy Policy

**[ Effective Date: March 9, 2010 ]** **AGREEMENT**  
LeanSpa, LLC(referred to hereafter as 'LS') owns and/or operates a network of websites offering a variety of products and services. In addition, LS collects consumer data from various other sources outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by LS. By using our website or submitting information to us, you consent to the use and sharing of information collected or submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use or visit any of LS's websites or web pages, and do not disclose any information to us. 

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**  
This Privacy Policy gives you an overview of LS's practices regarding the type of information collected, how we collect your information, how we use your information, how we share your information, and various other important facts about our privacy practices. Note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time, and we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at anytime. It is your responsibility to periodically revisit this Privacy Policy to review any changes. In order to track any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will include historical revision dates at the top of this document. We may also notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address you provided to us during registration via a LS website. It is your responsibility to provide us with your most current e-mail address. You may request that we refrain from using your personal information by clicking here to unsubscribe. 

**TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
We collect and merge non-personally identifiable information ('Non-PII') and personally identifiable information ('PII') through the various sources discussed below. For your reference, PII means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including but not limited to name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Non-PII is data that is not used to specifically identify, contact or locate an individual, including but not limited to zip code, gender, age, or IP address. 

**HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION**  
1\. Websites: We collect information about you via a LS website when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service or information. For example, if you decide to place an order or complete a registration form, we may ask you for, but not limited to, the following information: First and last name, delivery address, billing address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, mother's maiden name and/or payment information. We also collect information through web server applications. This information includes, but is not limited to your referring URL, browser type, Internet protocol ('IP') address, and the date and time.  
2\. Advertisements: Additionally, we collect information about you when you complete a questionnaire on one of our advertisements included on our websites or web pages. The advertisements present opportunities for consumers to acquire our services or gain access to other opportunities we can provide. This information may include, but is not limited to: your e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, IP address, and payment information; as well as other information about your interests. 

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**  
We may use your information collected for any legally permissible purpose at our sole discretion, including but not limited to those uses described in this Privacy Policy.   
LS may always use the personal information that you provide to: (1) fulfill your request for a product, information or other service; (2) respond to an e-mail or request; (3) send information to you about additional goods or services, deliver to you our newsletter or surveys, product information, usage tips or promotions; (4) help improve our website(s) or services; (5) to service your account, verify your identity, and provide customer service; or (6) customize visitors' experiences at our website(s). LS may also use your personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of itself and its affiliates and subsidiaries.   
We may use your information for ad serving purposes. For example we may show ads to you based on your IP address, demographics, phone number, or other information we collected about you. We reserve the right to decline all current and future transactions through any data points at our own discretion which may include the use of currently and previously collected information.  
Your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this website constitutes your express written consent to receive telemarketing calls from third-party marketers, including by means of a pre-recorded message and automated voice dialing. Your consent will be effective regardless of whether the number you have provided: (a) is a home, business, or cell phone line; and/or (b) is or will be registered on any state or federal Do-Not-Call (DNC) list, and shall remain in effect until you revoke your consent by clicking here to unsubscribe.  
When submitting your credit card to us or one of our advertisers, you are consenting to allowing us to pre-authorize your credit or debit card to determine your ability to pay for any product or service that you may be interested. We do not sell, release or share your credit card information with any third party. 

**HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**  
LS respects your privacy. We will never share your personal information with a third party, unless required by law. 

LS reserves the right to release current or past user information and Personal Information: a) in the event that we believe that the Website and/or the Service is being or has been used in violation of the Website Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; or b) if the information is subpoenaed. Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when LS, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time.  
Additionally, LS will use or disclose your personal information under the following circumstances: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) in the event you violate or breach an agreement with a LS website; (3) we believe you will harm the property or rights of a LS website's customers; or (4) we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, chargeback resolutions, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.   
We may also collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of a LS website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. Information gathered may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. 

**TECHNOLOGY**  
Some information is collected automatically while you are using a LS website. It is important to note that LS must store this information in order to ensure you receive optimal service while using a LS website. This type of information could include:   
1\. Log Files: LS uses log files to track member usage and engagement and to gauge the effectiveness of our different services. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the website. Log file information may include, but not limited to: (1) IP Addresses; (2) browser type; (3) number of page views; (4) log-in frequency; and (5) page or section accesses.  
2\. Cookies: LS may use cookies, which are electronic pieces of information stored on your computer, to allow us to recognize you when you return to a LS website and to provide you with customized services and information.  
3\. Clear Gifs: LS uses clear gifs, which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier (similar in function to cookies), to track the online movements of the web users.  
Additionally, we may use pixel tracking technology to track the completion of transactions with us or our advertisers. 

**CHILDREN**  
LS websites are not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 18 and instruct users under 18 not to send us any information. It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 18. We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. In particular, our intention is to fully comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ('COPPA'). Per COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with PII through any point of contact we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files when you click here to contact us.

**SECURITY**  
We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside of LS. However, perfect security does not exist on the Internet. Therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of your information. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with and providing information to LS.   
Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which LS sites or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a LS site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**OTHER LINKS**  
LS websites may contain links that direct you to websites owned and operated by other companies. LS does not control, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party websites, which may employ cookies and/or collection personal information. In addition, LS will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third-party website that you visit.

**OPT-OUT**  
By completing the registration form on one of the LS website or web pages you consented to receiving marketing communications from us and our third-party marketing partners, if you decide that you do not want to receive these marketing communications you may opt-out of receiving them at any time by clicking here to unsubscribe.

**CONTACTING US**  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, click here to contact us.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**  
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTES THAT ARISE OVER YOUR PRIVACY WILL BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IN ADDITION, YOU AGREE THAT LS'S LIABLITY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY LS. 

[ Previous Revisions: January 03, 2008; May 27, 2008, July 22, 2009, August 24, 2009, September 18, 2009] 

Privacy Policy | Contact Us | Unsubscribe
